The Sha Ryan Show is the only podcast on
the planet where you can discuss
floating alien technologies. You had a
encounter with a what we call monolithic
slab hovering off the ground at range 19
at a secret underground bunker. And so
we're here to document that testimony.
Cursed out content that can possess you.
This guy had watched a piece of
pornography and became possessed as a
result of it. The imminent risk of World
War II.
>> Let's talk about how close we are to
potential World War II and [music]
nuclear warfare.
>> Way too close.
>> And the most bizarre situations you can
think of.
>> And I was like, nah, it's cold. And he
leans forward. He like looks at my dick
and he goes, I see it's cold. It's
presented as mind-blowing firstirhand
information no one else can access. And
to be honest, some of the episodes are
genuinely incredible. But if you scroll
down to the descriptions, you will find
Sha says the episodes are for
entertainment value only. And how some
statements made by our guests may later
be found to be verifiably false, which
starts to put a different skew on some
of his most legendary conversations.
Take how Sha introduces this particular
guest with something rock solid. Every
once in a while, I will take a
speculative interview
where nobody really knows the truth on
the subject matter. And when I do that,
I always talk about that in the
introduction.
This interview, however, may be a little
bit hard for some of you to believe, but
I assure you there is no speculation.
The guest is Joseph Mcman Eagle, who was
involved in Stargate, the real CIA
psychic program that trained people to
see into each other's brains or even
other worlds. Stargate is really weird,
but this kind of sounds like speculation
to me.
>> Everything I described,
an old fort,
pyramids,
uh, big impact crater with a road
running through it. There's a there's a
road run straight as an arrow for 1,200
km
on Mars. I just thing is literally tens
of thousands of feet tall. What the hell
is it? There's no doubt in my mind that
what they're saying about this old city
is true.
>> And that's when you begin to feel that
the podcast comfortably oversteps a line
between truth and entertainment. Shawn
also drops a bombshell in the intro.
I've heard that this man actually remote
viewed his own death,
which supposedly happens at age 78.
Coincidentally,
this episode was recorded on his 78th
birthday. And I addressed that and ask
him this question in the episode. You'll
see it's at the very end. Nearly 6 hours
later, he asks that burning question
we've all been waiting for. But the
answer is less than dramatic.
>> It is my understanding that you
may have remote viewed your own death
and that it happens at age 78.
>> I don't know about that. 78. I did I did
have an incident when I went to Vietnam.
where I I thought I saw my imminent
death and it turned out to be a huge
assumption on my part.
>> Assumption actually happens to be one of
Joe's favorite words which seems quite
revealing of some of the claims he's
making.
>> Assumptions. Those assumptions. A lot of
assumptions. Assumptions.
>> Shan brought on another Stargate guest.
This time, Skip Atwater, a former US
Army counter intelligence special agent.
He gives us a very classic limited
hangout, which is basically what you're
always seeing when you see the CIA guys
on podcasts. It'll be when an
intelligence guy offers a small glimpse
into something new, leaving us to wonder
if it's true or just a lie.
>> Do you think they are continuing the
program under a different name?
>> No.
>> Why wouldn't they?
>> They already had
>> Did I say that? What are those programs?
>> I've long since not been a part of that.
26 years and 12 years retirement.
[music]
It's a long time ago and nobody would
have told me anyways.
>> He confirms those five other programs
exist and then just stops immediately.
It didn't go unnoticed by fans of the
show. I came on here asking the same
thing. This guy is full of [__] and is
so obviously trained in dancing around
questions instead of answering them.
Shawn should have called him out. At
this point, you can really see this is
enraging Shaun's viewers. Podcasts like
this, Driver CEO and Joe Rogan are
immensely powerful. People trust them
for highquality information outside of
the mainstream media. And Shawn
acknowledges that with Andrew Huberman.
He's doing intellectual jiujitsu.
Lex [music] is a podcast genius. He's
doing intellectual jiu-jitsu. Joe's a
podcast genius. Yeah,
>> he's blending all of his things, his
drive, his interest, his intense
curiosity, his comedy, [music] his
ability to highlight things with his
emotion in podcasting. And you're doing
the same by virtue of your work with
government and special operations
[music] and your intense curiosity.
Podcasting is real. It's one It's as
real as it gets. [music] And traditional
media, I think I sometimes look at it
still, but they're in competition with
us. We're not in competition with them.
It's a damn good way to put it, you
know. [clears throat] It's um it's
really it's just fascinating to watch
like these tables turn [music] and
they've turned.
>> They point out how podcasts are becoming
a source of truth for the entire media
ecosystem. If you look at the pace at
which they move and you look at the kind
of top contour of their of what they put
out and I'm going to just be blunt and
you look at what they're putting out, a
good percentage of it is just poached
off of podcasts now. And you can't
disagree with them entirely. Podcasts
are incredibly useful and they're
infinitely better than anything that CNN
or Fox News or the BBC is going to put
out. But a claim appears in a podcast,
gets chopped into a small clip, and then
turns into a Reddit thread, which then
becomes a national news story about what
was revealed on the podcast. By that
point, most people encountering it have
never even heard the original
conversation or any of its caveats. The
line between useful information and
entertainment bordering on fantasy can
get annoyingly blurry. Billy Carson runs
Forbidden Knowledge, a platform built on
ancient civilizations, lost technology,
and ancient astronauts. He makes some
unusual claims about Easter Island
>> there. Somebody went there and lit that
place on fire.
>> Yeah. They burned down the majority of
the Moai heads. [music] They they put
some type of a chemical on the Mois and
lit that on fire which melted solid
stone. [music]
>> When did this happen?
>> That happened in uh October of 2022.
>> And then comes out with this cool
sounding fact.
>> The peak of the pyramid,
>> yes,
>> is the average of all the peaks
>> on Earth. on Earth.
>> Everyone loves a story like this, but
these points are pretty easy to pull
apart, even by the conspiracy community.
Love the Sha Ryan show, but hate when he
puts people like this on. All the UFO
people he's had on were just [__]
artists. Billy's interview was fun, but
it's just a load of crap. It looks
tactical from Sha, who initially built
this alternative career on being
outspoken. Now he lets too many air
their wild theories for views, using his
incredible platform to delegitimize
incredible talking points. In the summer
of 2023, he ran three episodes back to
back under one banner, the UFO
whistleblower marathon, opening each one
with the same line.
>> Remember, all of these gentlemen
have testified in front of Congress
under oath.
>> This one is Eric Hecker, whose
background is one Antarctic season, 2010
to 2011, working as a plumber and
firefighter at the South Pole station.
>> It also has the capacity to transmit.
There are um embedded in the ice what
are called digital optical modules doms.
They're about the size of a basketball.
It is the world's largest telescope and
now because we [music] have proven that
it can transmit. It's the world's
largest directed energy weapons system.
It is responsible for the earthquakes in
Christurch New Zealand in 2011 on the
front end of the year. He's talking
about the Ice Cube Nutrino Observatory,
which is an unusual science project a
bit like CERN in Switzerland. Now, there
are some curiosities about Antarctica,
but nobody else who's ever worked at
that station has backed up Hecker's
version, and his story just sounds kind
of outrageous. While Sha's comments
always look clean and created, this
reaction fell through the cracks.
Sometimes this whistleblower business
feels like it's the actual scop. The
next whistleblower, Michael Herrera,
says his unit was doing earthquake and
tsunami relief in Sumatra in 2009 when
they suddenly saw this.
>> 300 ft is what I'm estimating about a
football field
>> and it was circular.
>> Circular. It's like an octagon because
it had like corners on it that was like
an octagon shape but still circular. And
the gear that they had was black OTV
vests. They had black camouflage
utilities.
>> It gets weirder when you learn this was
an alien human trafficking operation.
And he says there's not drugs that
they're put in these shipping
containers. He says it's humans.
>> Human trafficking.
>> Yes. His own words.
>> The Pentagon's UFO office reviewed his
account and found nothing to support it
and even noted he doesn't have the
documented record that real
whistleblowers like David Grush do. The
third in the marathon was Steven Greer.
His entire argument traces back to one
claim that in December 1993, he
personally proved CIA director James Wy
on UFOs at a private dinner. By 93, I
was [music] being asked to go up and
brief um the director of the CIA for
Bill Clinton, uh R. James Wolsey.
>> That letter then became the front page
of our UFO, where the very community
partial to his story pulled him apart.
The first thing I noticed about him was
his constant use of words like
debriefed, blackside, stood up, etc.
Sometimes I think he straight up enjoys
laughing as some sort of covert
operative in a deadly spy game. You
never hear him say no to anything
either. He has an answer for absolutely
everything.
>> General Albert Stubble personally
offered me $2 billion
to not pursue what I was doing and
become part of his team.
>> $2 billion
>> with a B, you know, in ' 92.
>> He even has the cheat to go after others
doing the same thing he is. The folks
that they will allow to talk about it
are people that have been cherrypicked
by this cabal, this secret government
group to say what they're told to say.
It's scripted.
>> Do you have any examples of this?
>> Yes, of course. Uh Nick Pope, Lou
Alzando, Chris [music] Melon, all those
guys.
>> Alzando was once exposed by Joe Rogan
who vocalized skepticism about the UFO
situation. whether or not they're just
using him as a useful idiot to just get
out some silly story because they're
covering up for the fact that there's
some very advanced drone system that the
United States government has they're
trying to keep under wraps.
>> But Greer also gives an open call live
on a show for people to come to his UFO
conference.
>> I would love to be there for that.
>> Yeah. Well, you're invited and um we
need as many media people and podcast
people there. Herrera was watching that
exact episode and went to the conference
with Sha.
>> So, we connected through Dr. Greer,
>> correct?
>> At his conference in DC, he brought in a
handful of whistleblowers. You were one
of them.
>> And even Billy Carson connected through
that same very tight-knit circle
controlled by Greer. So,
when we met at Guru's event, what are
the odds of so many independent
whistleblowers turning up at one
conference with mind-blowing UFO
encounters and then conveniently making
lucrative book deals and podcast
appearances. So, of course, many people
are just calling it what it is,
magnifying each other's messages,
propping up each other's careers, and
scratching each other's backs. The
whistleblower ecosystem is a built-in
advantage. Secrecy can protect a weak
story almost as effectively as it
protects a real secret. Documents are
classified, names deliberately hidden,
locations can't be revealed. So despite
the risk perceived by the audience, it's
a very safe content format at this
level. This has become a running theme
on the podcast. DC Long, a veteran
working with his dad, who was a building
contractor at the time, claimed they
were taken to an extremely secretive
hidden facility. I could see this giant
monolithic slab just sitting there. The
closer we got to it, I could feel this
intense vibration
and but you couldn't hear anything. It
was dead silent in there. It was about
20t long. It's about 7t tall.
>> It would be impossible for a human to
even think about picking something like
this up.
>> What does he have to do to never leak
this groundbreaking information to
anyone? Simply sign an NDA, which he of
course refuses. and he's like, "I need
you to sign this." And it was a nondis
an NDA.
And I was like, [laughter] "I'm not
going to sign that."
>> He says the whole project was shut down
after. It's an odd security model. Let
someone randomly walk up and view
floating alien rocks, then give them a
form to sign on their way out. And even
DC Long is connected to that same little
group. If you had to pick up something
like that to move it anywhere, you would
need at least three, four cranes.
>> Oh wow.
>> Here could tell you better.
>> Telling a fun story about aliens has
never been such an amazing career path.
And the closer you look, the more you
realize the SRS pattern can be a little
tougher to spot. Sarah Adams, a
sparkling military and intelligence
credentials, and she's a key source for
the show. Sarah Adams, co-author of
Benghazi: Know thy enemy, a cold case
investigation, former CIA officer,
Libyan crisis before, during, and after
the 9/11 attacks, counterterrorism
analyst, targeter for the CIA, senior
adviser on the select committee on
Benghazi. Her biggest claim is that
al-Qaeda has trained and deployed more
than a thousand fighters into the United
States.
>> Wait a minute. I just want to [music]
clarify. You are 100% certain that there
are 1,000 plus al-Qaeda trained fighters
within the United States borders.
[music]
>> Well, al-Qaeda says they trained and
deployed a thousand for this attack.
First off, I think there's more than a
thousand al-Qaeda members in the United
States. But for the Homeland attack,
that number is based on what al-Qaeda is
saying, so they could exaggerate.
>> Remember, the source of the number is
al-Qaeda's own propaganda. And she flags
that it might be inflated. She's also
not really an outside source. She's a
staff member at SRS with her own
newsletter.
>> Like I said, it's a free CIA
intelligence briefs.
>> We all know by now that the CIA press
office vets every single thing anyone
says publicly about intelligence. But
it's Sarah who brought Shawn his most
mysterious guest. Sarah Adams, a really
good friend of mine and [music] uh
repeat guest on Shawn Ryan showed us uh
what [music] about a month ago, I think.
Yeah.
>> And um so I know you're traveling from
overseas. We'll not say where, but um
she says that you are the world's
leading expert on al-Qaeda.
>> Totally anonymous Jane Doe. And the
pitch really cranks up the stakes.
>> You're one of the leading experts in the
world regarding the al al-Qaeda
terrorist network. You're an ISAF
veteran and former intelligence analyst.
You completed multiple tours in
Afghanistan. Now listen to how Sarah's
number is conveniently repackaged here.
>> Sarah had mentioned that there is a at
least at least 1,000 terrorists that
have infiltrated the United States. I'm
surprised that it's not more.
>> Well, my numbers are are quite the same.
>> Sean stripped the caveat. Jane do also
raised suspicions when she said this.
>> I mean, the United States has its
database, right? Big part of it is
coming from Afghanistan.
>> Mhm. you know, you had all the names,
the backgrounds.
Um, Europe doesn't have this big
database. If they are sharing between I
mean between Europe or or the United
States, I I I don't know that.
>> She doesn't know if Europe and the US
share intelligence and is hesitant over
simple questions even the audience can
answer.
>> You don't you have I don't know. I don't
know what happened on the meeting, but I
found it interesting. But the GDI, I
don't know. The third one, I don't know
the name. I don't know how it's going to
work. I I really don't know it. I don't
think so. I mean, I don't think so. And
I don't want to be
>> But it's the next guest that brings it
full circle. Joe Londale co-founded
Palanteer and then a defense company
called Eperis. Unidentified drones had
just appeared over New Jersey, and Sha
brought him on to explain, but he opens
by disclosing their relationship. But it
just so happens that uh you know I've
been super interested in your company
Eperis and uh I've had several
conversations with your business partner
Grant for Standing and um and uh love
him. Amazing guy.
>> Then he asks the question, "What the
hell do you think these drones are?" I
mean, know I actually don't know the
answer.
>> The title promised an answer to the
mystery. The guest doesn't have one, but
it's not long before we find out the
real purpose of this discussion. Eperus
is a directed energy basically a
directed EMP weapon and it is I mean
it's it seems to me from the reading
I've done on it it's it's defense
against drones.
>> You know the tests have shown you can do
about 100 drones at a time. So I think
our [music] stadiums are going to need
to be defended by things like this.
>> Sean wants to strengthen the pitch and
he gives that same number hardening one
more notch. Also these terrorists are
very well trained now.
>> I had uh a former CIA targeter in here
just a couple days ago. We just released
the interview now and uh actually
yesterday and uh she's talking about,
you know, there there are at least 1,000
very well-trained terrorists within our
borders right now.
>> Yeah, it pisses me off, man. That's
crazy.
>> So, put it together. A speculative
statistic mentioned by show staff was
passed on like Chinese whispers and then
ended up in the pitch to sew a
cuttingedge weapon. This big mystery
turned out to be research drones and
hobbyists. One employee later admitted,
"You remember that big UFO scare in New
Jersey? Well, that was us." Blending
speculation with hard facts might
explain why Sha started adding those
disclaimers in the first place. This is
Rob O'Neal, who built his whole
post-military career on the apparent
fact that he was the one to take out
Osama bin Laden.
>> He's not surrendering. He's He's got to
have a suicide belt. So, I shot him
twice when he was standing up and I shot
him again on the floor.
>> Where'd you shoot him?
>> I shot him in the face three times.
Yeah, you just killed Osama bin Laden.
Your life just changed. Get to work.
That story is extremely compelling and
has sold millions in books and speaking
fees for years, featuring on big Netflix
documentaries exposing how he took down
Bin Laden and saved the day. But this
video's title has changed. It used to be
the man who killed Bin Laden. Now it's
disputed claims surrounding the Bin
Laden raid. So, how could this have
happened? Well, it started when a second
guy from the raid turned up on SRS with
a different story. cleared to the door
of the room, looked in, and he's
basically twitching at the foot of his
bed.
>> Bin Laden's just twitching foot.
>> Head shot from the guy coming up the
stairs. [music] We didn't want to shoot
him in the face. Nobody wanted to. We
wanted the photo, right? He published a
book that was investigated by the
government, which ordered him to pay
back the profits.
>> So, I pay $3,800 a month for the next 15
years. They said if I miss one payment,
they'll charge me back taxes and come
after me again. Sha tries to get him to
directly contradict O'Neal and claim he
killed Bin Laden, which just would have
caused chaos, but he keeps his story
straight. Did you shoot Bin Laden
>> on the [music] ground? Yes,
>> you did.
>> Yeah.
>> How many times?
>> Couple.
>> Where at?
>> The body.
>> And the body. How did that feel?
Don'ting tell me like I'm just doing the
job. [__] You just [music] killed
you shot.
>> I didn't kill Ben. I've never said I
killed Ben. Matt Bison quickly became
the most trusted personality of the two.
The American special forces agreed with
him and rejected O'Neal. Rob O'Neal was
obviously the loudest of the people who
claimed to have killed UBL, but a lot of
people doubt his story, and he has been
inconsistent in telling it. But O'Neal
hasn't stopped. He even appeared in the
Netflix documentary, which again really
pissed off the community. And he's now
suing two podcasters for saying he
wasn't the one who killed Bin Laden. So,
you've got to give Shan some credit for
changing the title, even if O'Neal has
been doubted for years and never
challenged him on it once. And it wasn't
the first time an investigation was
stamped over a thumbnail. Tim Kennedy
was introduced as a milestone for his
channel.
>> I found him to be an incredible human
being. Perfect guest for 100.
>> And by all accounts, he's had an
incredible life. He lived in a small
town in California, ravaged by a serial
killer, and he magically found the
perfect wedding ring at the bottom of
the sea. I see this glimmer of this ring
or of this metal and I swim over there
and I fan it and I find a size 14 Irish
Ba band band titanium wedding ring. I
grab it and I swim back up to the top
and I'm like,
Sabrina, look what I just found. It's an
[snorts] Irish band. I'm Kennedy. I'm ob
obviously Irish. But he was eventually
exposed when he was finally forced to
admit he'd lied about receiving the
Bronze Star with Valor. Welcome back to
the channel everybody. And yes, if you
haven't seen it already, Tim Kennedy
finally after seven long gruelling
months put out this halfass admission,
half-assed apology, finally sort of
admitting to the fact that he lied
multiple times about having valor awards
and bronze medals with valor. Kennedy's
problem was a medal he never earned. The
next guest problem is a country he was
never actually in. John McY's story is
about jumping into a live war zone.
>> Man, I jumped in Iraq in ' 91, but it
was 30 knot winds and it up a ton of
dudes. I think there was like, man, it
had to be like I don't I I don't know,
man. It was a lot. Like 80 backboards
out there with dudes taped to them. You
know what I mean? Like,
>> but the military community soon started
picking that apart, too. He could have
misremembered Q8 as a rack, but then you
notice the pattern of scrutiny running
through his other appearances, which may
explain why he says this when he gets
into the gritty details. Do you know
what I mean? Like, you know what I mean?
Like, you know what I mean? Like, you
know what I mean? You know what I mean?
>> But at least Father Chad Riper's
credentials aren't in question. He's a
real Catholic priest with a doctorate in
philosophy. He was also granted the
authority to perform exorcisms over
watching one
>> where uh this guy had watched a piece of
uh became possessed as a result of it.
All [music] I know is that once I
watched that piece of became completely
obsessed with the woman that was in
[music] the so I spent all my time
trying to find her and all the other
forms of that I could find where she had
acted in it. on. He's probably
directionally right. It
>> it was the Satanists in the 30s, 40s,
and 50s that taught the people in
Hollywood that if you curse the master
copy, all of the subsequent copies made
from that [music]
will bear the curse and it can influence
people. But it illustrates why Sha
listed some of his content as
entertainment only. Sha is generally
quiet in all of these episodes and is
anything but a skeptic. At least he
doesn't act it. He behaves much more
like Steven Butler in the diary of the
CEO. You can see it when he talks to Dr.
Diane Hennessy Powell from the John
Hopkins University. She came on to give
a signature bombastic story on autistic
children who can see the future and they
all happened to be at a school she
worked at. All of the [music] kids were
scoring 100% on the on the math tests.
They were all they knew that Emma was
really good at math [music] and so they
were just cheating by you know
telepathically seeing well what is how's
Emma answering these. So one day Emma
decided that she was going to prove that
that's what was going on and so she
purposely put false answers to [music]
the math questions there and then all of
the rest of the class gave the same
wrong answers.
>> The test she gave for this are all
bizarre.
>> She said, "What am I thinking right
now?" and she was thinking of the the
dinosaur Barney and she typed Barney
who's my landlord and she she types
helmet that was the name of her landlord
and then how do you say I love you in
German which [music] the this therapist
she was fluent in German and then Haley
typed it out German for I love you
>> landlords dinosaurs German three tests
three easy hits to give the public
ultimately no one is saying his show
isn't packed with great stories fun
moments and genuinely thoughtprovoking
themes in fact I love his podcast but
Sha has reinvented himself self as a
counterculture kind of guy who's going
up against the establishment while
simultaneously platforming politicians
like Vance Trump and Kennedy. He's very
willing to air whatever story anyone can
dream up. Whether it be exorcisms or
UFOs, but once a podcast reaches this
scale, it becomes the destination when
you want a story to travel. And that
flips the incentives. Dodgy stats are
being repackaged and used to sell
weapons in the podcast's business
interests. And there's a lot of
promotion going on aside from Palunteer
Defense Technologies, not least Sean's
own vigilante gummy bears. Everybody
gets a gift.
Even you. [laughter]
And uh here you go. You're welcome.
You're welcome. So, those are Vigilance
Elite Gummy Bears. Everybody gets a gift
here.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Nothing crazy. Just a little something
for the ride home.
Those are
>> [music]
>> uh Vigilance Elite Gummy Bears.
Everybody gets a gift.
>> Yes, I brought some for you, too.
>> Oh, I love that.
>> So, this is an exchange. You want me to
do this first? I do know about the gummy
bears. Get [music] everybody a gift. And
I was going to get you a Delta Sky
Miles.
>> Oh, thank you.
>> These are gummy bears.
>> I got you a couple of gifts here.
>> Oh, very good.
>> So,
actually three of them.
>> First one,
Vigilance League gummy bears. Everybody
on the show gets a gift.
So, little something for you. And those
are not poisoned. I promise.
>> No. Hey,
>> they're just gummy bear.
>> Because now you want to go on the show
to crank up your claim and distort it to
stand out to finally get the views. A
claim buried inside hours of normal
conversation feels like you'll get away
with it. And really, media personalities
of all kinds move towards podcasts
because they were tired of information
being filtered through institutions. But
Sha's show shows how the institutions,
companies, politicians, and intelligence
have simply just followed them there.
We've already seen the mass influx of
XCIA operatives and intelligence chiefs
flooding the arena, queuing up to profit
from current events. It's perfectly
reasonable to some extent. John Kiyaku
admitted himself he does this to make
money. Rob O'Neal said he makes up to
75K every time he talks about shooting
bin Laden. But that means we're stuck in
this weird ecosystem where you can't
always understand what's going on under
the hood. No one from the real
establishment or the opportunists
looking to make a few dollars has to
actually control the podcast. They just
have to understand how it works and how
[music] to use it to get their message
across.